Soon, the person Onii-chan
loved in his past life,
as well as his little sister
from his past life,
and the teacher he's indebted
to in this life, will come here.
Onii-chan said I didn't have
to tell them about myself,
but if these people are important
to him, then I also want to...
We're already here?
We are.
Yes.
It only took a second.
Teleportation is awesome!
Yes, it is.
It's beautiful here.
Onii-chan!
Welcome home!
Um, I'm back.
Wow.
Beast people really exist here!
Welcome to the village of the Spirit People.
Lady Aishia, it has been some time.
It is an honor to see you once more.
We are honored.
Is Aishia-oneechan super important?
The People of the Spirit
view high-level spirits
that can materialize and
take human form as divine.
I feel like maybe we shouldn't
casually call her Ai-chan.
I-I'm so sorry.
I don't need any formalities.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Celia Claire.
Rio has told me about you.
You're his little sister, aren't you?
Y-Yes!
I apologize for the abruptness of
this request. You have a lovely tail.
May I touch it for a moment?
What?
Um, yes.
Oh, it's so fluffy!
I wonder if she likes snuggling fluffers.
She definitely does.
Celia-san...
Then this might be paradise for her!
What?
That was...
She spoke Japanese, right?
Yes!
Just like Onii-chan, I have
memories from my past life.
So I nominate myself to
be your Strahlian teacher!
Are you sure about this, Latifa?
Yes, it's what I decided.
I've already told Sara-oneechan and
the others, and the Eldest, too.
And I know how it feels to be anxious
because you've come from another world.
Plus, I'm your little sister!
I want to be able to help you.
I see. All right.
Thank you, Latifa.
I'm happy you feel that way.
We haven't introduced ourselves yet.
We, along with Latifa,
will be helping you to become
accustomed to life in the village.
My name is Sara.
I am Orphia.
I'm Alma.
We are very pleased to meet you.
I'm Sendo Aki, and this is my little brother.
I'm Masato.
My name is Ayase Miharu.
I'm very pleased to meet you.
She's the one...
She's the person Onii-chan was in love with.
Spirit Chronicles 2
It's so relaxing, isn't it?
That tickles!
This feels so good.
Welcome Home
Everyone in the village is waiting
to meet you. I'll take you to them.
Could it be that people are...
afraid of us?
Well, Aki-neechan's face
is pretty scary, after all.
What do you mean?
You siblings really are close.
Hardly!
No way!
See? You're completely in sync!
The people of this village keep
their distance from humans.
I think some of this reaction is
due to the rarity of all of this.
Oh.
What?
Hello.
What's wrong?
Apparently, your school uniform is unusual.
What?
Is it strange?
We're going to meet the Eldest,
so I tried to dress formally.
It isn't strange.
Yeah, she said it's cute!
Really? I'm glad.
I think your ears are cute.
I really like them.
It's nothing.
Miharu-san, would it be all right
if I called you Miharu-oneechan?
Of course you can!
And may I call you Latifa-chan?
Yes! And I want you to tell me all
about yourself, Miharu-oneechan!
I'd be happy to!
Will you let me join in?
And me, too!
Of course!
Yay!
We'll all be friends!
Wow! What a feast!
Masato, don't get too excited.
It's unbecoming.
It's a welcome party, so you don't
have to worry about formalities.
To think that they went to the
trouble of a welcome party for us.
It's so nice, isn't it? And there
are so many fluffy people here!
Celia, that's all you've been talking about.
I'm seeing a different side of the professor.
Lady Aishia, seeing you again makes us,
the People of the Spirits, overjoyed.
Children from another world, Mistress Celia,
welcome to the village of
the People of the Spirits.
They may be from another world,
but looking at them like this,
they're just humans.
Don't stare at our guests with
that craggy face of yours.
You're scaring them.
Aishia, Rio, it has been some time.
Yes.
Lady Dryas.
Wow!
Awesome!
Oh! Lady Dryas!
And now, in celebration
of this chance meeting!
Cheers!
Now we drink! Now we carouse!
Yeah!
How nice! Thank you!
The od of the other-worlders
is amazing. It looks delicious.
It is delicious.
What?
Aki-neechan! They have inarizushi!
There you go again.
They can't possibly have—
They do!
I made them!
I thought they might be nostalgic
for you. Have some if you like.
I will. Thank you for the treat!
It's delicious!
I'm so glad!
Everyone really likes Haruto-san, and he's
really nice. He's a good big brother.
He is! I'm proud to call him my big brother!
I'm jealous.
What?
I want to hurry up and
see my big brother, too.
I wonder where he is right now.
I want to go looking for him.
I want to hurry up and be
able to speak the language.
I'll study really hard!
Okay!
We've arrived!
From now on, this will be your home.
Wow!
It's huge!
How lovely!
It's wonderful.
Miharu-oneechan, you and the
others can use this room.
Whoa!
Thank you!
You must all be tired.
Feel free to use the open-air bath.
And rest as long as you like.
You heard them!
An open-air bath? All right!
This feels so good.
It's so relaxing, isn't it?
That tickles!
Man. Why'd I go and lose?
Rock, paper, scissors!
I win!
Well, we'll head in first!
I should've asked you to do it,
Haruto-niichan. You'd have won for sure.
I don't know about that.
Want to try it and see?
Rock, paper, scissors!
You can see the stars.
You're right! Wow.
We've really ended up somewhere
incredible, haven't we?
I wonder if we'll ever be able to go home.
Yes, I'm sure we will... one day.
Haruto-niichan, why are you so strong?
You're always crazy strong, no matter
what's going on, right? Why is that?
I'm not, really. It's just...
There's something I have to do.
Something you have to do?
Yes, and to do it, I have to get stronger.
I want to, too.
I want to get strong so I can protect
Miharu-neechan and Aki-neechan!
I see.
Onii-chan!
The bath is free now!
Shall we go?
Yeah!
Spirit Chronicles 2
Professor! Good morning.
Rio... Good morning.
You're up early.
Yes. It's so pleasant here and the
air is so fresh. It's a lovely place.
Thanks to all of that,
I woke early, refreshed.
I see.
Professor, I'm sorry.
What?
I'm sorry to have kept
you waiting for so long.
Thanks to Latifa, Miss Sara, and everyone,
Miss Miharu and the others
have settled into the village
more quickly than I anticipated.
Let's deliver a letter to your parents.
Thank you.
But you aren't overtaxing yourself, are you?
Overtaxing?
I know that you're working hard to return
Miharu and the others to their world.
I want to support you in that.
But what about you, Rio?
Me?
You said that you'd been able to
erect a tombstone for your parents,
but there was more. Something...
Something that I got in the way of
because you came to save me, right?
That's why you don't have
to do anything for me.
Thank you for worrying about me.
It's true that I still have
things that I must do.
But, Professor, you aren't in the way.
Back then, I...
More than anything else,
I wanted to save you, Professor.
Rio...
Sending those three home is the same.
So, after we've delivered your letter,
I plan to head to Rodania to
gather information on the Heroes.
All right. Thank you for
telling me all of that.
And if you ever need me for anything,
don't hesitate to tell me, all right?
After all, I happen to be
the mage with the most magic of anyone
in the Kingdom of Beltrum!
That's incredible.
You don't really think that.
Yes, I do!
No matter what happens,
I'm on your side, Rio.
Onii-chan, Big Sis Celia,
Big Sis Aishia, have a safe trip!
We will.
We'll be back.
Yes.
You can leave the rest to me!
Thank you.
There's no need to worry about things here.
And it seems Miharu has a gift for you.
It's...
I've made obento for you.
Please eat it, if you'd like.
Thank you.
It must have been hard work,
getting up early and making all of this.
Not at all.
We've been leaving everything
to you, Haruto-san.
And now you're even going back to
the Strahl region for our sakes.
This is the only thing I could do for you.
Please don't let it bother you.
I'm doing this because I want to.
Thank you.
I promise that one day we will repay
this debt of gratitude to you.
This bento is more than enough.
We'll eat it with thanks.
I hope it suits your tastes.
Don't worry! I love your cooking, Miharu-san.
Miharu worked really hard
to make that for you.
Big Sis Miharu was really acting
the part of a wonderful wife!
Haruto-niichan, while you're away,
I'm gonna work hard at all sorts of stuff!
Right.
Everyone, we're going now.
Professor Celia? Aishia.
Have a good trip!
I hope that Haruto-san
and the others stay safe.
Now, before Onii-chan comes back,
you should all get fluent in
Strahlian and surprise him, right?
Time to study!
Yeah!
Yes!
Beltrum Kingdom, Rodania, Capital of Marquis Rodan's Lands
And so, we would like for Sir Sakata Hiroaki,
who is also a Hero,
to attend our kingdom's party.
That is why I have come on His Majesty's
behalf to deliver an invitation.
And of course, Princess Flora, Duke Huguenot,
Lady Roanna, you three are invited as well.
I would love to agree immediately,
but I'm afraid the decision
rests with Sir Hiroaki.
There is still time before the party.
I have no intention of pressing
anyone for a ready answer.
Please take as long as you
like to think it over.
Everything, even down to her
voice, is just too cute.
Flora and Roanna are pretty high-level,
but this situation with a noble girl from
a neighboring kingdom just hits me harder.
You're telling me this is when the
star character appears? Seriously?
Um, Sir Hiroaki?
Huh? Oh!
It's a party to introduce your Hero, right?
Why not? I'll go.
You'll be there, right, Liselotte?
That is my intention.
Then it's decided. I'll go, too.
I'm certain His Majesty will be overjoyed.
I look forward to seeing the
Hero again at the party.
Haruto, we've reached Cleia.
All right.
Kingdom of Beltrum, Cleia, Capital of Count Claire's Lands
Professor Celia, this is
where you grew up, isn't it?
Yes.
And that's the house where
I was born and raised.
There's a secret passage in the garden
that connects to the main house.
Only the family knows about it,
so we should be able to leave
the letter inside and return.
Do you think we can make it from here?
Yes. It's over there.
I'm afraid the guards might spot us.
We'll use spirit arts
to hide us from here on.
I'll perform the spirit arts.
Pardon my familiarity.
Professor, please open the entrance
before the guard returns.
Leave it to me.
There!
I'll help.
Thank you.
It looks like we've been detected.
Let's hurry.
Yes.
What is going on?
I can't imagine that any
outsiders could have gotten in.
Professor.
Could it be my Celia?
Is that you, Celia?
Father, Mother, it's Celia.
I am sorry to have caused you so much worry.
But please be at ease.
Right now, I am living a safe,
peaceful life with people whom I trust.
I know that in abandoning my marriage into
Duke Arbor's family, I've disappointed you,
but I wanted you to know that one thing.
And one day, I will return
to see you again.
When I do, I will explain everything.
Until then, please take care
of yourselves and stay healthy.
With gratitude for your
unwavering love and kindness,
Celia Claire.
Celia! My little Celia!
Celia!
Lord Roland! What's wrong?
It... It's nothing.
You haven't disappointed us.
We'll see each other again.
That's a promise! My dear Celia.
Are you sure you don't want to see them?
Yes, for now. This is for the best.
All right.
Thank you, Rio.
Let's come back sometime.
Next time, you'll be able to see
them in person. I'm certain of it.
Yes.
Yes, we must do that.
Next is Rodania, right?
Yes.
Lady Liselotte, we are
about to land in Amande.
Aria! Thank you.
What was that?
I will find out immediately.
Natalie! Cosette!
Lady Liselotte!
Chloe! What's happened?
A-A dragon! A black dragon has appeared!
A dragon?
Because of that,
our ship is being forced to make an
emergency landing in a nearby town!
Next Time
Heroes and Champions
"Heroes and Champions."
Spirit Chronicles 2
Illustration: Minazuki Futago